CZARINA JOY T. EVANGELISTA

· 3305 Sillawit, Cauayan City Isabela

Phone: 09970671406 Gmail: czarinaevangelista01@gmail.com GitHub: https://github.com/CzaPH
Portfolio URL: Personal Portfolio Website (czaph.github.io)

Targeting an internship or entry level opportunity in Software Engineering. Upcoming Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (BSIT) graduate with a strong foundation in leadership and programming principles across multiple platforms.

- Experienced in developing, testing and debugging code; and designing interfaces.
- Quickly learn and master new technologies; successful working in both team and self-directed setting.

EXPERIENCE

CAPSTONE PROJECT MANAGER AND DEVELOPER OF "SMART STUDENT CLASS ATTENDANCE MONITORING SYSTEM".

2018-2019

HUMSS REPRESENTATIVE, BASIC EDUCATION SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL LEVEL, SUPREME STUDENT GOVERNMENT OF UNIVERSITY OF PERPETUAL HELP SYSTEM LAGUNA – ISABELA CAMPUS.

2021-2022

PRESIDENT, COLLEGE OF COMPUTING STUDIES INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY (CCSICT)

College based organization President.

2022-2023

CCSICT GOVERNOR, SUPREME STUDENT COUNCIL OF ISABELA STATE UNIVERSITY – EHAGUE CAMPUS (ISU-E)

Currently the CCSICT representative in the Supreme Student Council, the highest governing student organization in the ISU-E.

EDUCATION

ELEMENATRY: 2013

RIZALUNA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL

Honor Student.

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL: 2017

UNIVERSITY OF PERETUAL HELP SYSTEM – LAGUNA ISABELA CAMPUS

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL: 2019

UNIVERSITY OF PERETUAL HELP SYSTEM – LAGUNA ISABELA CAMPUS

GRADUATE OF HUMANITIES AND SOCIAL SCIENCES STRAND. LEADERSHIP EXCELLENCE AWARD – SILVER MEDAL. SCHOOL PAPER AWARD.

TERTIARY: 2023

ISABELA STATE UNIVERSITY – MAIN CAMPUS

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY.
MAJOR IN WEB AND MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT.

RELEVANT SKILL

- HTML
- CSS
- GitHub
- Vue.Js

- JavaScript
- PHP
- MySQL

ACTIVITIES

LEADERSHIP TRAINING AND SEMINAR ATTENDED

- 28TH YOUNG MEN CHRISTIAN ASSOCIATION (YMCA) NATIONAL ASSEMBLY OF HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS AND 21ST YMCA NATIONAL SCHOOL CLUB ADVISERS' SEMINAR.
- 29TH YMCA NATIONAL ASSEMBLY OF HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS AND 22ST YMCA NATIONAL SCHOOL CLUB ADVISERS' SEMINAR.
- 12TH ICT ROADSHOW SEMINAR HELD AT DEVE NECIA HALL, ISABELA STATE UNIVERSITY EHCGAUE CMAPUS.
- STRATEGIC PLANNING OF THE SUMPREME STUDENT COUNCIL OF ISABELA STATE UNIVERITY ECHAGUE CAMPUS.
- LEADERSHIP CONVERGENCE AT ISABELA STATE UNIVERITY ECHAGEU CAMPUS.

1ST NATIONAL SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL RESEARCH CONGRESS HELD AT UNIVERSITY OF SAINT LUIS, TUGUEGARAO, CAGAYAN.

ONE OF THE RESEARCHERS OF "FEDERALIZATION: LEVEL OF AWARENESS OF GRADE 12 STUDENTS ON FEDERALISM." RESEARCH PAPER CHAMPION IN THE CATEGORY OF FEDERAL ARTS AND POLICY STUDIES.

ONLINE WEBINARS ATTENDED

- CYBERTALKS: A WEBINAR ON CRYBERSECURITY.
- WEB APPLICATION SECUTITY TESTING USING OPEN-SOURCE TOOLS.

- COMMUNITY IGNITE #8: A DAY OF A LIFE OF A CODER: WHAT IT TAKES TO BE A PROFESSIONAL SOFTWARE DEVELOPER.
- COMMUNITY IGNITE SERIES #9 GROWING AS YOUNG PROFESSIONALS: GETTING STARTED IN TECH INDUSTRY.
- COMMUNITY IGNITE #11: HOW TO BE YOU PO?? RECIPE TO BECOMNG A VUE.JS DEVELOPER.
- 11TH ICT ROADSHOW WITH THE TOPICS:
 - DIGITAL GRAPHIC ENHANCEMENT.
 - CRYBERSEUCIRTY AND DIGITAL LITERACY.
 - APPLICATION OF ARTIFICIAL INTELEGENCE.
 - IMPORTANT ASPECT OF THESIS AND CAPSTONE PROJECT.

REFERENCES

AILEN LABUGEN

MANAGER OF PASCUAL AGRI SUPPLY 0926-124-6901 AUNT

WENDELL M. CASTILLO, MIT

COLLEGE SECRETARY AND CCSICT STUDENT BODY ORGANIZATION (SBO) ADVISER 0906-448-4258
COLLEGE INSTRUCTOR AND SBO ADVISER

RENALYN G. TECSON, MIT

BSIT PROGRAM CHAIR 0945-366-1261 COLLEGE INSTRUCTOR AND PROGRAM CHAIR